We'll use value counts on the start date column.
我们将对 Startdate 列使用 value_counts
Now we have 6,856 entries in the start date column that have ASAP as their value,
现在 我们 Startdate 列有 6,856 个条目 它们的值为 ASAP
and all of these phrases in ASAP list are nowhere to be seen in this output.
在此输出结果中 根本看不到 ASAP 列表中的所有这些短语
However, because Panda hides some of the entries from us here,
然而 因为 Pandas 隐藏了部分条目
we can't exactly be sure that everything was fixed though,
所以 我们不能只根据这个输出结果
with this output alone.
完全肯定所有问题都已修复
And expanding this output and scrolling through all of the entries,
展开输出 滚动查看所有条目
isn't a great use of our time.
会浪费我们的时间
In cases like these,
在这类情况下
we can borrow a technique from software testing here, assert statements.
我们可以借鉴软件测试的技术 即 assert 语句
This is another type of programmatic assessment.
这是另一种编程评估
Assert statements look like this.
Assert 语句是这样的
Assert, then a logical statement that evaluates to TRUE or FALSE.
Assert 逻辑语句 评估真值或假值
For example, two plus two equals five,
比如 二加二等于五
which is obviously false.
显然是假的
When Python encounters an assert statement like this,
当 Python 遇到一个像这样的 assert 语句
if the logical statement is false,
如果逻辑语句为假
Python will yell at us with an assertion error to
Python 将显示 AssertionError
let us know that the thing we were testing wasn't true,
以提醒我们测试对象不为真
at which point we try to see where things went sideways, assertion error.
这时候 我们会尝试看看哪方面出错 即 AssertionError
Two plus two equals five isn't true.
二加二等于五非真
If that statement is true, nothing happens.
如果该语句为真 则不会发生任何事情
Nothing is good for assert statements.
assert 语句不会返回什么好结果
We'll use the assert statement to test that our second cleaning operation worked.
我们将利用 assert 语句来测试第二项清理操作是否奏效
Again, like when we were cleaning,
重申一下 当我们在清理的时候
we needed to write a for loop because there are so many entries here.
我们必须编写一个 for 循环 因为这里有如此多的条目
You'll have to do the same thing when testing.
测试时 你也必须做同样的事情
So will copy and paste the structure of this for loop,
复制、粘贴 for 循环的结构
put it down here, get rid of this.
把它放在这里 删掉这个
In the quiz ahead,
在接下来的练习题中
verify that all the similar phrases to ASAP in
验证 ASAP 列表中与 ASAP 类似的所有短语
ASAP list were actually converted to
实际上都已通过这个循环主体中的 assert 语句
ASAP using an assert statement in the body of the this loop.
转换成 ASAP